Guide to the Allen Ginsberg film and video archive, 1983 - 1996
Department of Special Collections
- Ginsberg Poetry Reading Part I. (Box 7, Folder 61)
  Time in: 1:01:03 Time out: 1:20:10 Total Time: 19m 7s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Ginsberg performs live on the University of Colorado campus, Macky Auditorium, Boulder, CO, July 24, 1989. Ginsberg introduces each poem briefly before reading it.
  - Intro by Peter Michelson. (Folder 61)
    Time in: 1:01:38 Time out: 1:07:40 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Michelson tells an anecdote of Blake and compares Ginsberg's and Blake's style of agitating.
  - Ginsberg's intro. (Folder 61)
    Time in: 1:09:40 Time out: 1:12:10 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The last days of Abbie Hoffman's mother.
  - "CIA Dope Calypso". (Folder 61)
    Time in: 1:12:40 Time out: 1.17.43 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg sings poem.
  - "Whom Bomb". (Folder 61)
    Time in: 1:18:39 Time out: 1:20:16 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A sound poem.
- Ginsberg Poetry Reading, Part II. (Box 7, Folder 62)
  Time in: 2:01:00 Time out: 2:23:19 Total Time: 22m 19s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "In Society". (Folder 62)
    Time in: 2:01:28 Time out: 2:02:42 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "In Society..." Out: "... dominating the whole room."
  - "Pull My Daisy". (Folder 62)
    Time in: 2:03:19 Time out: 2:04:37 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Pull My Daisy..." Out: "... gap be shut."
  - "Tonight, All Is Well". (Folder 62)
    Time in: 2:04:57 Time out: 2:05:19 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Tonight All Is Well..." Out: "... sleepless on the couch."
  - "Song". (Folder 62)
    Time in: 2:06:04 Time out: 2:07:42 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Song..." Out: "... where I was born."
  - "A Supermarket In California". (Folder 62)
    Time in: 2:07:59 Time out: 2:10:08 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Supermarket in California" Out: "... black waters of Leathy."
  - "Sunflower Sutra". (Folder 62)
    Time in: 2:12:04 Time out: 2:17:02 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Sunflower Sutra..." Out: "... sit-down vision."
  - "America". (Folder 62)
    Time in: 2:19:10 Time out: 2:23:19 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Includes an explanation of important figures in the poem. In: "America..." Out: "... Ewig-Weibliche made me --"
- Ginsberg Poetry reading, Part III. (Box 7, Folder 63)
  Time in: 3:01:00 Time out: 3:19:16 Total Time: 18m 16s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "America" (cont'd). (Folder 63)
    Time in: 3:01:00 Time out: 3:02:06 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: " -- them bad Russians..." Out: "... queer shoulder to the wheel."
  - "Kaddish" (Abridged). (Folder 63)
    Time in: 3:04:25 Time out: 3:14:12 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: " And it's the last moment..." Out: "... death fall of flowers."
  - "On Neal's Ashes". (Folder 63)
    Time in: 3:14:49 Time out: 3:15:33 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "On Neal's Ashes..." Out: "... all ashes again."
  - "Uluru". (Folder 63)
    Time in: 3:17:18 Time out: 3:19:06 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "When the red pond fills..." Out: "... worlds come to their end."
- Ginsberg Poetry Reading, Part IV. (Box 7, Folder 64)
  Time in: 4:01:00 Time out: 4:22:51 Total Time: 21m 51s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "Yaweh and Allah Battle". (Folder 64)
    Time in: 4:01:04 Time out: 4:06:26 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Yaweh and Allah Battle..." Out: "... Salaam"
  - Short poems about Allen Ginsberg's Father's decline. (Folder 64)
    Time in: 4:07:38 Time out: 4:08:59 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Feeble arms..." Out: "... mixed up with stones."
  - "Father Death Blues". (Folder 64)
    Time in: 4:09:02 Time out: 4:12:34 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A solo song by Ginsberg.
  - "Put Down Your Cigarette Rag". (Folder 64)
    Time in: 4:14:05 Time out: 4:18:54 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "Maturity". (Folder 64)
    Time in: 4:19:22 Time out: 4:19:41 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Maturity..." Out: "... vomit air."
  - "Irritable Vegetable". (Folder 64)
    Time in: 4:19:49 Time out: 4:20:27 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Irritable Vegetable..." Out: "... eat hotdogs."
  - Allen's Haikus. (Folder 64)
    Time in: 4:21:10 Time out: 4:22:44 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Six 17 syllable one-line poems read by Ginsberg.
- Ginsberg Poetry Reading Part V. (Box 7, Folder 65)
  Time in: 5:01:00 Time out: 5:15:12 Total Time: 14m 12s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "Sphincter". (Folder 65)
    Time in: 5:02:59 Time out: 5:03:46 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "I hope my good old..." Out: "... 'til death, relax."
  - "Cosmopolitan Greetings". (Folder 65)
    Time in: 5:05:13 Time out: 5:08:13 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Stand up against..." Out: "... Candor ends paranoia."
  - "Personals Ad". (Folder 65)
    Time in: 5:09:28 Time out: 5:10:41 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Poet professor in autumn..." Out: "... 10009, New York."
  - "Proclamation". (Folder 65)
    Time in: 5:10:50 Time out: 5:11:20 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: " I am king of the universe..." Out: "... every word I say."
  - "Do the Meditation". (Folder 65)
    Time in: 5:12:00 Time out: 5:12:54 Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Dick Cavett Show, with Allen Ginsberg. (Box 7, Folder 66)
  Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:26:00 Total Time: 26m 0s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Dick Cavett's nighttime in depth PBS television show, 1978.
  - Poem: "Don't Grow Old". (Folder 66)
    Time in: 1:18:44 Time out: 1:21:10 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "My Father Died..." Out: "... it was a glue factory."
  - Song: "Father Death Blues". (Folder 66)
    Time in: 1:22:16 Time out: 1:25:57 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Father Death Blues..." Out: "... as time will tell."
- Kaddish. (Box 7, Folder 67)
  Time in: 10:00:27 Time out: 10:59:32 Total Time: 59m 5s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A WNET (PBS) television program. Ginsberg reads and comments on his poem "Kaddish" combined with a one-act off Broadway play based on "Kaddish". This show aired in 1977.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:01:02 Time out: 10:01:57 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg describes the Kaddish, the Hebrew prayer for the dead.
  - Scenes from the play: "Kaddish". (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:01:58 Time out: 10:03:07 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    These are scenes reenacted on the streets.
  - Allen Ginsberg reads the poem "Kaddish" in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:03:08 Time out: 10:09:24 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads the opening of the poem.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:09:25 Time out: 10:10:06 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg describes how this really is a poem addressed to the dead.
  - Allen Ginsberg reads the poem "Kaddish" in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:10:07 Time out: 10:10:48 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads on...
  - Scenes from the play: "Kaddish". (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:10:49 Time out: 10:12:30 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen Ginsberg reads the poem "Kaddish" in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:12:31 Time out: 10:12:55 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Scenes from the play: "Kaddish". (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:12:56 Time out: 10:15:10 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen Ginsberg reads the poem "Kaddish" in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:15:11 Time out: 10:16:31 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The reading continues...
  - Allen Ginsberg interview in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:16:32 Time out: 10:18:35 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg looks at photos of his younger self and comments on his inner turmoil.
  - Allen Ginsberg reads the poem "Kaddish" in his Manhattan apartment interwoven with scenes from the play. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:18:36 Time out: 10:24:25 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads on as visuals of the play intermittently appear over Ginsberg's voice.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:24:26 Time out: 10:27:01 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg holding a photo of himself at the age of 12 visiting his mother in the institution. He calls this photo "the heart of 'Kaddish'".
  - Allen Ginsberg reading the poem "Kaddish" in his Manhattan apartment interwoven with scenes from the play. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:27:02 Time out: 10:30:30 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Allen Ginsberg interview in his Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:30:31 Time out: 10:32:32 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg discusses more family history.
  - Allen Ginsberg reading the poem "Kaddish" in his lower east side apartment interwoven with scenes from the play. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:32:33 Time out: 10:54:00 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The reading continues as visuals of the play intermittently appear over Ginsberg's voice.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview in his lower east side of Manhattan apartment. (Folder 67)
    Time in: 10:54:01 Time out: 10:57:15 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg discusses how he dealt with his anger towards his mother. Ginsberg shows his amazing number of government files obtained through the Freedom of Information Act.
- Fried Shoes, Cooked Diamonds, Part I. (Box 7, Folder 68)
  Time in: 0:01:00 Time out: 0:30:10 Total Time: 28m 50s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A film by Costanzo Allione, 1979. This English language Italian documentary about Naropa in 1978 includes interviews of all relevant Beat personalities and events of that year.
- Fried Shoes, Cooked Diamonds, Part II. (Box 7, Folder 69)
  Time in: 0:31:46 Time out: 1:01:30 Total Time: 29m 44s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg and William Burroughs, Part I. (Box 7, Folder 70)
  Time in: 21:02:16 Time out: 21:59:00 Total Time: 24m 56s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, Summer 1983.
  - Ginsberg and Burroughs on Naropa steps (ambient sound). (Folder 70)
    Time in: 21:02:12 Time out: 21:03:04 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Exterior shots of Naropa with Burroughs and Ginsberg on the front steps.
  - Ginsberg and Burroughs on Naropa steps (synch sound). (Folder 70)
    Time in: 21:07:57 Time out: 21:12:04 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Burroughs and Ginsberg begin an interesting discussion, but road noise becomes overpowering and the interview moves indoors.
  - Ginsberg and Burroughs at Allen's house on Bluff Street in Boulder, CO. (Folder 70)
    Time in: 21:29:15 Time out: 21:37:17 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Burroughs and Ginsberg continue their discussion inside.
- Allen Ginsberg and William Burroughs, Part II. (Box 8, Folder 71)
  Time in: 20:00:10 Time out: 20:05:30 Total Time: 5m 20s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, Summer 1983. Burroughs and Ginsberg conclude their discussion inside.
- William Burroughs Interview. (Box 8, Folder 72)
  Time in: 16:49:00 Time out: 17:45:44 Total Time: 23m 35s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, August 7, 1983. Jump in time code from 16:59:00 to 17:33:03. Picture and sound out of synch at times.
- Eugene Brooks Interview. (Box 8, Folder 73)
  Time in: 3:00:00 Time out: 3:18:00 Total Time: 18m 0s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Plain View, NY, January 5, 1985.
- Carl Solomon Interview. (Box 8, Folder 74)
  Time in: 1:00:07 Time out: 1:05:17 Total Time: 5m 10s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Carl Solomon at Ginsberg's Solomon Gallery exhibit, New York City, January 6, 1985.
- Edith Ginsberg Interview, Part I. (Box 8, Folder 75)
  Time in: 22:02:20 Time out: 22:32:08 Total Time: 11m 14s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Patterson, NJ, January 5, 1985. Jumps in Time Code.
- Edith Ginsberg Interview, Part II. (Box 8, Folder 76)
  Time in: 22:32:08 Time out: 22:08:00 Total Time: 27m 37s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Patterson, NJ, January 5, 1985. Jumps in Time Code. Picture out at 23:03:53, sound continues. Colorbars and voice 23:06:23 - 22:08:00.
- John Hammond Sr. Interview. (Box 8, Folder 77)
  Time in: 13:02:02 Time out: 13:16:18 Total Time: 11m 45s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Columbia Records office, New York City, January 15, 1985.
- Abbie Hoffman Interview. (Box 8, Folder 78)
  Time in: 7:35:00 Time out: 7:46:37 Total Time: 11m 37s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Denver, CO, 1985.
- Amiri Baraka Interview. (Box 8, Folder 79)
  Time in: 5:21:30 Time out: 5:43:11 Total Time: 21m 40s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, 1985.
- Herbert Huncke Interview (Box 8, Folder 80)
  Time in: 22:44:00 Time out: 23:30:00 Total Time: 24m 56s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  New York City, January 16, 1985. Jumps in Time Code. Picture out at 23.40.00, sound continues.
- Ken Kesey Interview. (Box 9, Folder 81)
  Time in: 18:35:31 Time out: 19:12:45 Total Time: 10m 26s Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Boulder, CO, 1983. Jumps in Time Code.
- Allen Ginsberg Poetry Reading, Part I. (Box 9, Folder 82)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:34:00 Total Time: 34m 0s Source: S-VHS Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: 3/4" Master
  Allen Ginsberg performance, Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, June 30, 1992. Stage left.
- Allen Ginsberg Poetry Reading, Part II. (Box 9, Folder 83)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:41:00 Total Time: 41m 0s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, June 30, 1992. Poetry readings by: Steven Taylor, Anne Waldman, Anselm Hollo.
- Allen Ginsberg Poetry Reading, Part III. (Box 9, Folder 84)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:35:00 Total Time: 35m 0s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Allen Ginsberg performance, Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO, June 30, 1992. Stage right.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part I. (Box 9, Folder 85)
  Time in: 10:00:00 Time out: 10:29:00 Total Time: 29m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Ginsberg's last interview for Life and Times of Allen Ginsberg, Boulder, CO, July 17, 1992.
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part II. (Box 9, Folder 86)
  Time in: 11:00:00 Time out: 11:29:00 Total Time: 29m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part III. (Box 9, Folder 87)
  Time in: 12:00:00 Time out: 12:28:00 Total Time: 28m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part IV. (Box 9, Folder 88)
  Time in: 13:00:00 Time out: 13:29:00 Total Time: 29m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part V. (Box 9, Folder 89)
  Time in: 14:00:00 Time out: 14:29:00 Total Time: 29m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  End of Ginsberg's last interview for Life and Times of Allen Ginsberg, July 17, 1992. Interview continues with Allen reading poems.
  - "After Lalon" Stanza I. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:10:54 Time out: 14:11:20 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "It's true..." Out: "... up shit's creek."
  - "After Lalon" Stanza II Take 1. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:11:23 Time out: 14:11:48 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "I sat..." Out: "... dreaming all along."
  - "After Lalon" Stanza II Take 2. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:11:52 Time out: 14:11:17 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "After Lalon" Stanza III. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:12:24 Time out: 14:13:08 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "It's 2am..." Out: "... Allen Ginsberg."
  - "After Lalon" Stanza IV. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:13:11 Time out: 14:13:30 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Sleepless..." Out: "... middle of the night."
  - "After Lalon" Stanza V, Take 1. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:13:39 Time out: 14:14:29 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "4am..." Out: "... will it really come true?"
  - "After Lalon" Stanza VI, Take 1. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:14:31 Time out: 14:14:50 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "I had my chance..." Out: "... path to extinction."
  - "After Lalon" Stanza V, Take 2. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:15:48 Time out: 14:16:40 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "After Lalon" Stanza VI, Take 2. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:16:46 Time out: 14:17:04 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - "After the Big Parade". (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:17:22 Time out: 14:17:58 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "After the Big Parade..." Out: "... for the next rejoicing."
  - "Return of Kral Majales", Take 1. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:18:05 Time out: 14:18:29 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Return of Kral Majales" Out: "... paper crown."
  - "Return of Kral Majales", Take 2. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:18:34 Time out: 14:19:48 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Return of Kral Majales" Out: "... so Ah!"
  - "At the Grave of My Father", by Louis Ginsberg. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:20:34 Time out: 14:21:49 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "At the Grave of My Father Out: "... tribute from your son."
  - One-Line Poems. (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:22:50 Time out: 14:25:45 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Several one-line poems.
  - "Going to Chicago". (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:25:58 Time out: 14:27:40 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Going to Chicago" Out: "... metal microphone."
  - "Grant Park". (Folder 89)
    Time in: 14:28:00 Time out: 14:28:57 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Grant Park" Out: "... Garden of Eden?"
- Allen Ginsberg Interview, Part VI. (Box 9, Folder 90)
  Time in: 15:00:00 Time out: 15:13:00 Total Time: 13m 0s Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  July 17, 1992. Ginsberg reading poems on this tape as listed below.
  - "From Memory Gardens". (Folder 90)
    Time in: 15:00:09 Time out: 15:01:37 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "From Memory Gardens..." Out: "... drunken dumb show."
  - "Returning to the Country for a Brief Visit", Take 1. (Folder 90)
    Time in: 15:02:16 Time out: 15:03:57 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "Returning to the Country..." Out: "... glacier peak with Gary."
  - "Returning to the Country for a Brief Visit", Take 2. (Folder 90)
    Time in: 15:04:11 Time out: 15:04:42 Source: Beta Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    In: "robins and sparrows..." Out: "... glacier peak with Gary."
  - "Brooklyn College Brain". (Folder 90)